clicksocean.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Last Updated: September 21, 2016
What do we do
Clicks Ocean (http://clicksocean.com here and after “site”, “website”) is the advertising network that facilitates the
‘bidded’ buying and selling of online media advertising inventory for publishers, advertisers, advertising agencies and
advertising networks.
This privacy policy describes how and why Clicks Ocean collects personally identifiable data from users and website
visitors, publishers and end users of publisher sites to Clicks Ocean, and how such data will be used. Clicks Ocean is
committed to respecting the privacy of personal identifiable data and anonymous user data gathered and futher
dissemination.
Information Collection
While our registration process, we ask publishers, advertisers, advertising agencies and advertising networks, users to
provide contact information, for example: name, e-mail, IP address, physical address, telephone numbers and etc. We
may also request a unique login password, and confirmation that you have accepted our terms and conditions of use.
If required to complete a transaction, we might also request financial information including paypal account or credit card
numbers. You may modify the information you have provided at any time from within your personal request to the
following e-mail: support@clicksocean.com.
We use customer contact information to provide services and occasionally, provide information on our company. The
customer’s contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. We use unique identifiers, such as login
& password, to verify the user’s identity and as account numbers in our customer database system. Unless required to
complete a transaction you have requested, or to perform maintenance on our site, we do not share personal identifying
information with outside entities.
Cookies
We use “cookies” on our site to associate certain Internet-related information about you. Cookies are small text files
placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing a more customized website experience. We also use cookies to
estimate the number of unique visitors to the site and provide aggregate information about our user base.
In addition, our member’s advertisements may contain cookies. While we use cookies in certain sections of our Web site,
cookies received with banner ads are collected by the advertising company and we do not have access to this
information. You may delete the cookies on your machine by following the instructions provided with your Internet
browser software.
How We Use Information Collected
Clicks Ocean uses personally identifiable data collected from users and website visitors in order to:
       •To improve the quality and functionality of the website, enhance your experience, create new services (including

      customized services), change/cancel existing content and services, or for other internal and statistical purposes.
      •To present you relevant content, marketing materials and advertisements, by analyzing your interests from the
      web pages you visit and online services that you use.
      •To provide you with support and handle inquires.
      •To enforce our terms of use and/or EULA.
      •To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies as required.
      •To conduct surveys and market research.
      •To improve the quality and functionality of the website, enhance your experience, create new services (including
      customized services), change/cancel existing content and services, or for other internal and statistical purposes.
      •To present you relevant content, marketing materials and advertisements, by analyzing your interests from the
      web pages you visit and online services that you use.
With respect to data collected via the Clicks Ocean network site, we may combine Personal Information with data
collected from other sources and disclose the Personal Information and combined information to participating advertisers
and ad networks so that they can determine whether to bid on ad inventory and in order to improve the relevance of the
advertising presented to Users. Examples of such data include: (a) country, city, and other geo-location details based
upon the IP address of the User; (b) category and keyword information based upon the Publisher website URL; and (c)
other data from advertisers and data providers that would help in ad targeting (e.g., an advertiser that wants to advertise
to Users who have previously visited the advertiser’s website).
How we protect the Collected Information.
Information that we collect is stored on servers that Clicks Ocean solely manages, using standard security procedures
and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access,
destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. If we learn that we have unexpectedly stored personal information (e.g., if
we become aware that a URL that we store contains personal information), we will use commercially reasonable efforts
to anonymize or purge this information.
Changes to Policy
From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy. Therefore, it is recommended that you read it periodically. All
substantial changes made to this policy will be notified on the website, at our sole discretion, and will take effect
immediately.
Dissemination of Information
Your Personal Information will not be shared unless we have first given you notice that we might share your data, and
you have authorized us to do so. The Company receives information from you and other individuals who use the website
(Advertisers and Partners), and have the right to use this data, but is generally prohibited from sharing this information
with other companies or people
Your Information will not be linked with your Personal Information or be shared, unless we have given you notice as
described above and you have given us authorization to do so.
In case you have any other queries regarding privacy information, please contact us at support@clicksocean.com
